payworldindia.com 2011-02-22

# PayWorld :: EVDS, Electronic Voucher Distribution System - Privacy Policy

www.payworldindia.com website is the property owned and operated by the “Sugal and Damani Utility Services Pvt. Ltd” 

**Security and Protection of your Personal Details**

We at pay world are committed to maintain the security and privacy of all your personal information obtained by you on our website. We take significant precautions to protect your Personally Identifiable Information both online and offline. Maintaining a high degree of confidentiality and privacy and secure transmission of data is of utmost important for us. You can view your Credit card security card guarantee back up system by clicking the link provided at the bottom of each page on our site. Our system is configured with the data encrypting technology and firewall system. The data that you enter in our website is protected by 128-bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) which ensures the safe transmission of data.We also have a digital Certificate from “thawte”,Inc,a top maker of hardware and software used to protect and manage computer network access, certifying the secure nature of our site. 

All our servers at pay world storing the customer’s information are kept in a secure environment and are accessed by only limited number of authorized employees of our company. 

**Information Collected from You**

We collect the customers information such as your name, address, telephone numbers, e-mail addresses and other information that can identify you as a specific individual ("Personally Identifiable Information"). 

**We collect Personally Identifiable Information when you:**

• Become authorized to use our site through a Site Partner  
• Purchase a product or service  
• Request further information regarding a product or service  
• Disconnect a service  
• Contact us

**Purchase Information  
**

We collect you credit card information for the billing of your services and products that you wish to purchase, which includes your card number, card type, card Holder name, address and expiration date.

**Requests for Further Information Regarding Products and Services**

In case you require additional information and have any query regarding product and services, we collect your personal information to contact you and respond to your query. 

**Our Service Providers**

Pay world offers an application service provider (ASP) to the computer-based services to customers over a network. The most important sense of this business is that of providing access to a particular application program using a standard protocol such as HTTP. In addition, the issues of upgrading have been eliminated from the end-firm by placing the onus on the ASP to maintain up-to-date services, 24 x 7 technical support, physical and electronic security and in-built support for business continuity and flexible working.

Pay world Clients for ASP services include businesses, government organizations, and membership organizations.

**Cookies**

We do not track or collect information about your visits to other Internet sites. Certain technical information is automatically collected about your computer each time you request a page during a visit to this site. This information may include your IP address, operating system and Web browser software (e.g., Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer). We assign you a "cookie" (i.e., a tiny packet of identifying information passed between your browser and a Web site) each time you visit this site. You do not provide this information? It is collected automatically as a means for supporting your visit to this site. This cookie does not contain any Personally Identifiable Information. You can always choose to not receive a cookie file by enabling your Web browser to refuse cookies or prompt you before accepting a cookie. Please be aware that by refusing to accept a cookie you will not be able to make optimal use of this site. Cookies are small bits of data that are stored by your browser. You can accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings of your web browser. 

**Use of Your Personally Identifiable Information**

Personally Identifiable Information collected on this site may be used to:

• Facilitate your orders for services and products  
• Send notifications  
• Promote our service and other available services and products  
• Respond to your questions or suggestions  
• Improve the quality of our site  
• Sharing Your Personally Identifiable Information

**Responses to Your Questions or Suggestions**

We will use your e-mail address or telephone number to respond when you submit a question or suggestion, or request assistance with using or accessing this site.

**Note:** We do not sell, share or rent your Personally Identifiable Information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.

**Notifications of Changes**

We reserve the right to modify or amend this Privacy and Security Statement at any time and for any reason with out prior notice.
